<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><ListRecords><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:gr-qc/9210004</identifier></header><metadata><title>The Spacetime Approach to Quantum Mechanics</title><description>  Feynman's sum-over-histories formulation of quantum mechanics is reviewed as
an independent statement of quantum theory in spacetime form. It is different
from the usual Schr\&quot;odinger-Heisenberg formulation that utilizes states on
spacelike surfaces because it assigns probabilities to different sets of
alternatives. Sum-over-histories quantum mechanics can be generalized to deal
with spacetime alternatives that are not &quot;at definite moments of time&quot;. An
example in field theory is the set of alternative ranges of values of a field
averaged over a spacetime region. An example in particle mechanics is the set
of the alternatives defined by whether a particle never crosses a fixed
spacetime region or crosses it at least once. The general notion of a set of
spacetime alternatives is a partition (coarse-graining) of the histories into
an exhaustive set of exclusive classes. With this generalization the
sum-over-histories formulation can be said to be in fully spacetime form with
dynamics represented by path integrals over spacetime histories and
alternatives defined as spacetime partitions of these histories. When
restricted to alternatives at definite moments of times this generalization is
equivalent to Schr\&quot;odinger-Heisenberg quantum mechanics. However, the quantum
mechanics of more general spacetime alternatives does not have an equivalent
Schr\&quot;odinger-Heisenberg formulation. We suggest that, in the quantum theory of
gravity, the general notion of &quot;observable&quot; is supplied by diffeomorphism
invariant partitions of spacetime metrics and matter field configurations. By
generalizing the usual alternatives so as to put quantum theory in fully
spacetime form we may be led to a covariant generalized quantum mechanics of
spacetime free from the problem of time.
</description><date>1992-10-07</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:gr-qc/9210006</identifier></header><metadata><title>The Quantum Mechanics of Closed Systems</title><description>  A pedagogical introduction is given to the quantum mechanics of closed
systems, most generally the universe as a whole. Quantum mechanics aims at
predicting the probabilities of alternative coarse-grained time histories of a
closed system. Not every set of alternative coarse-grained histories that can
be described may be consistently assigned probabilities because of quantum
mechanical interference between individual histories of the set. In the quantum
mechanics of closed systems, containing both observer and observed,
probabilities are assigned to those sets of alternative histories for which
there is negligible interference between individual histories as a consequence
of the system's initial condition and dynamics. Such sets of histories are said
to decohere. Typical mechanisms of decoherence that are widespread in our
universe are illustrated. Copenhagen quantum mechanics is an approximation to
the more general quantum framework of closed subsystems. It is appropriate when
there is an approximately isolated subsystem that is a participant in a
measurement situation in which (among other things) the decoherence of
alternative registrations of the apparatus can be idealized as exact. Since the
quantum mechanics of closed systems does not posit the existence of the
quasiclassical domain of everyday experience, the domain of the approximate
aplicability of classical physics must be explained. We describe how a
quasiclassical domain described by averages of densities of approximately
conserved quantities could be an emergent feature of an initial condition of
the universe that implies the approximate classical behavior of spacetime on
accessible scales.
</description><date>1992-10-12</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:gr-qc/9210010</identifier></header><metadata><title>Classical Equations for Quantum Systems</title><description>  The origin of the phenomenological deterministic laws that approximately
govern the quasiclassical domain of familiar experience is considered in the
context of the quantum mechanics of closed systems such as the universe as a
whole. We investigate the requirements for coarse grainings to yield decoherent
sets of histories that are quasiclassical, i.e. such that the individual
histories obey, with high probability, effective classical equations of motion
interrupted continually by small fluctuations and occasionally by large ones.
We discuss these requirements generally but study them specifically for coarse
grainings of the type that follows a distinguished subset of a complete set of
variables while ignoring the rest. More coarse graining is needed to achieve
decoherence than would be suggested by naive arguments based on the uncertainty
principle. Even coarser graining is required in the distinguished variables for
them to have the necessary inertia to approach classical predictability in the
presence of the noise consisting of the fluctuations that typical mechanisms of
decoherence produce. We describe the derivation of phenomenological equations
of motion explicitly for a particular class of models. Probabilities of the
correlations in time that define equations of motion are explicitly considered.
Fully non-linear cases are studied. Methods are exhibited for finding the form
of the phenomenological equations of motion even when these are only distantly
related to those of the fundamental action. The demonstration of the connection
between quantum-mechanical causality and causalty in classical phenomenological
equations of motion is generalized. The connections among decoherence, noise,
dissipation, and the amount of coarse graining necessary to achieve classical
predictability are investigated quantitatively.
</description><date>1992-10-20</date></metadata></record></ListRecords>