<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><ListRecords><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:hep-th/9406058</identifier></header><metadata><title>Maintaining coherence in Quantum Computers</title><description>  The effect of the inevitable coupling to external degrees of freedom of a
quantum computer are examined. It is found that for quantum calculations (in
which the maintenance of coherence over a large number of states is important),
not only must the coupling be small but the time taken in the quantum
calculation must be less than the thermal time scale, $\hbar/k_B T$. For longer
times the condition on the strength of the coupling to the external world
becomes much more stringent.
</description><date>1994-06-09</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:hep-ph/9406398</identifier></header><metadata><title>The Search for the Decay of Z Boson into Two Gammas as a Test of Bose
  Statistics</title><description>  We suggest that Bose statistics for photons can be tested by looking for
decays of spin-1 bosons into two photons. The experimental upper limit on the
decay $Z \rightarrow \gamma \gamma $ is used to establish for the first time
the quantitative measure of the validity of Bose symmetry for photons.
</description><date>1994-06-26</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:cond-mat/9406116</identifier></header><metadata><title>Negative Kinetic Energy Between Past and Future State Vectors</title><description>  An analysis of errors in measurement yields new insight into classically
forbidden quantum processes. In addition to &quot;physical&quot; values, a realistic
measurement can yield &quot;unphysical&quot; values; we show that in {\it sequences} of
measurements, the &quot;unphysical&quot; values can form a consistent pattern. An
experiment to isolate a particle in a classically forbidden region obtains a
negative value for its kinetic energy. It is the {\it weak value} of kinetic
energy between past and future state vectors.
</description><date>1994-06-29</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:cond-mat/9407011</identifier></header><metadata><title>Quantum Noise Limits for Nonlinear, Phase-Invariant Amplifiers</title><description>  Any quantum device that amplifies coherent states of a field while preserving
their phase generates noise. A nonlinear, phase-invariant amplifier may
generate less noise, over a range of input field strengths, than any linear
amplifier with the same amplification. We present explicit examples of such
nonlinear amplifiers, and derive lower bounds on the noise generated by a
nonlinear, phase-invariant quantum amplifier.
</description><date>1994-07-03</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:cond-mat/9407022</identifier></header><metadata><title>Two-Bit Gates are Universal for Quantum Computation</title><description>  A proof is given, which relies on the commutator algebra of the unitary Lie
groups, that quantum gates operating on just two bits at a time are sufficient
to construct a general quantum circuit. The best previous result had shown the
universality of three-bit gates, by analogy to the universality of the Toffoli
three-bit gate of classical reversible computing. Two-bit quantum gates may be
implemented by magnetic resonance operations applied to a pair of electronic or
nuclear spins. A ``gearbox quantum computer'' proposed here, based on the
principles of atomic force microscopy, would permit the operation of such
two-bit gates in a physical system with very long phase breaking (i.e., quantum
phase coherence) times. Simpler versions of the gearbox computer could be used
to do experiments on Einstein-Podolsky-Rosen states and related entangled
quantum states.
</description><date>1994-07-05</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:quant-ph/9707040</identifier></header><metadata><title>W(infty)-Covariance of the Weyl-Wigner-Groenewold-Moyal Quantization</title><description>  The differential structure of operator bases used in various forms of the
Weyl-Wigner-Groenewold-Moyal (WWGM) quantization is analyzed and a
derivative-based approach, alternative to the conventional integral-based one
is developed. Thus the fundamental quantum relations follow in a simpler and
unified manner. An explicit formula for the ordered products of the
Heisenberg-Weyl algebra is obtained. The W(infty) -covariance of the
WWGM-quantization in its most general form is established. It is shown that the
group action of W(infty) that is realized in the classical phase space induces
on bases operators in the corresponding Hilbert space a similarity
transformation generated by the corresponding quantum W(infty) which provides a
projective representation of the former $W_{\infty}$. Explicit expressions for
the algebra generators in the classical phase space and in the Hilbert space
are given. It is made manifest that this W(infty)-covariance of the
WWGM-quantization is a genuine property of the operator bases.
</description><date>1994-07-21</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:cond-mat/9409111</identifier></header><metadata><title>Results on two-bit gate design for quantum computers</title><description>  We present numerical results which show how two-bit logic gates can be used
in the design of a quantum computer. We show that the Toffoli gate, which is a
universal gate for all classical reversible computation, can be implemented
using a particular sequence of exactly five two-bit gates. An arbitrary
three-bit unitary gate, which can be used to build up any arbitrary quantum
computation, can be implemented exactly with six two-bit gates. The ease of
implementation of any particular quantum operation is dependent upon a very
non-classical feature of the operation, its exact quantum phase factor.
</description><date>1994-09-26</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:gr-qc/9411004</identifier></header><metadata><title>Probabilities Don't Matter</title><description>  It is suggested that probabilities need not apply at all to matter in the
physical world, which may be entirely described by the amplitudes given by the
quantum mechanical state. Instead, probabilities may apply only to conscious
perceptions in the mental world. Such perceptions may not form unique sequences
that one could call individual minds.
</description><date>1994-11-01</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:hep-ph/9411270</identifier></header><metadata><title>Past-Future Interference in $\Phi$-Decays into Entangled Kaon Pairs</title><description>  Quantum interference effects between past and future events (neutral kaon
transitions, including CP violating decays) are discussed for entangled kaon
pairs produced through $\phi \to K^0 \bar{K^0}$ in $\phi$-factories.
Contrasting with the exciting conclusions of other recent analyses, we predict
the inexistence of such an observable effect.
</description><date>1994-11-11</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:gr-qc/9411035</identifier></header><metadata><title>Pedestrian notes on quantum mechanics</title><description>  I present an elementary essay on some issues related to nonrelativistic
quantum mechanics, which is written in the spirit of extreme simplicity, making
it an easy-to-read paper. Moreover, one can find a useful collection of ideas
and opinions expressed by many well-known authors in this vast research field
</description><date>1994-11-13</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:hep-th/9411094</identifier></header><metadata><title>On the Local Equilibrium Condition</title><description>  A physical system is in local equilibrium if it cannot be distinguished from
a global equilibrium by ``infinitesimally localized measurements''. This should
be a natural characterization of local equilibrium, but the problem is to give
a precise meaning to the qualitative phrase ``infinitesimally localized
measurements''. A solution is suggested in form of a Local Equilibrium
Condition, which can be applied to linear relativistic quantum field theories
but not directly to selfinteracting quantum fields. The concept of local
temperature resulting from LEC is compared to an old approach to local
temperature based on the principle of maximal entropy. It is shown that the
principle of maximal entropy does not always lead to physical states if it is
applied to relativistic quantum field theories.
</description><date>1994-11-14</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:gr-qc/9411044</identifier></header><metadata><title>How and why the wave function collapses after a measurement</title><description>  We explain the collapse of the wavefunction with the notion that, in a
measurement, the system observed nucleates a first order phase transition in
the measuring device. The possible final states differ by the values of
macroscopic observables, and their relative phase is therefore unobservable.
The process is irreversible, but needs no separate postulate.
</description><date>1994-11-16</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:gr-qc/9411053</identifier></header><metadata><title>Remarks on the frequency spectra of some fundamental quantum effects</title><description>  Short remarks on the problem of assigning frequency spectra to Casimir,
sonoluminescence, Hawking, Unruh, and quantum optical squeezing effects are
presented
</description><date>1994-11-20</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:hep-th/9411172</identifier></header><metadata><title>Classical and quantum representation theory</title><description>  These notes present an introduction to an analytic version of deformation
quantization. The central point is to study algebras of physical observables
and their irreducible representations. In classical mechanics one deals with
real Poisson algebras, whereas in quantum mechanics the observables have the
structure of a real non-associative Jordan-Lie algebra. The non-associativity
is proportional to $\pl^2$, hence for $\pl\raw 0$ one recovers a real Poisson
algebra. This observation lies at the basis of `strict' deformation
quantization, where one deforms a given Poisson algebra into a $C^*$-algebra,
in such a way that the basic algebraic structures are preserved. Our main
interest lies in degenerate Poisson algebras and their quantization by
non-simple Jordan-Lie algebras. The traditional symplectic manifolds of
classical mechanics, and their quantum counterparts (Hilbert spaces and
operator algebras which act irreducibly) emerge from a generalized
representation theory. This two-step procedure sheds considerable light on the
subject. We discuss a large class of examples, in which the Poisson algebra
canonically associated to an (integrable) Lie algebroid is deformed into the
Jordan-Lie algebra of the corresponding Lie groupoid. A special case of this
construction, which involves the gauge groupoid of a principal fibre bundle,
describes the classical and quantum mechanics of a particle moving in an
external gravitational and Yang-Mills field.
</description><date>1994-11-23</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:hep-th/9411173</identifier></header><metadata><title>Observation and superselection in quantum mechanics</title><description>  We attempt to clarify the main conceptual issues in approaches to
`objectification' or `measurement' in quantum mechanics which are based on
superselection rules. Such approaches venture to derive the emergence of
classical `reality' relative to a class of observers; those believing that the
classical world exists intrinsically and absolutely are advised against reading
this paper. The prototype approach (Hepp) where superselection sectors are
assumed in the state space of the apparatus is shown to be untenable. Instead,
one should couple system and apparatus to an environment, and postulate
superselection rules for the latter. These are motivated by the locality of any
observer or other (actual or virtual) monitoring system. In this way
`environmental' solutions to the measurement problem (Zeh, Zurek) become
consistent and acceptable, too. Points of contact with the modal interpretation
are briefly discussed. We propose a minimal value attribution to observables in
theories with superselection rules, in which only central observables have
properties. In particular, the eigenvector-eigenvalue link is dropped. This is
mainly motivated by Ockham's razor.
</description><date>1994-11-23</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:hep-th/9411175</identifier></header><metadata><title>Aharonov-Bohm Scattering of a Localized Wave Packet: Analysis of the
  Forward Direction</title><description>  The Aharonov-Bohm scattering of a localized wave packet is considered. A
careful analysis of the forward direction points out new results: according to
the time-dependent solution obtained by means of the asymptotic representation
for the propagator (kernel), a phenomenon of auto-interference occurs along the
forward direction, where, also, the probability density current is evaluated
and found finite.
</description><date>1994-11-23</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:hep-th/9411193</identifier></header><metadata><title>Information Loss in Black Holes and/or Conscious Beings?</title><description>  In 1976 Stephen Hawking proposed that information may be lost from our
universe as a pure quantum state collapses gravitationally into a black hole,
which then evaporates completely into a mixed state of thermal radiation.
Although this proposal is controversial, it is tempting to consider analogous
processes that might occur in certain theories of consciousness. For example,
one might postulate that independent degrees of freedom be ascribed to the
mental world to help explain the feeling of a correlation between one's desires
and one's choice of actions. If so, one might ask whether information in the
physical world can be lost to such postulated degrees of freedom in the mental
world. Or, one might hypothesize that the mental world can affect the physical
world by modifying the quantum action for the physical world in a
coordinate-invariant way (analogous to the alpha parameters in wormhole
theory).
</description><date>1994-11-25</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:hep-th/9411196</identifier></header><metadata><title>Protective Measurements</title><description>  Protective measurements yield properties of the quantum state of a single
quantum system without affecting the quantum state. A protective measurement
involves adiabatic coupling to the measuring device together with a procedure
to protect the state from changing. For nondegenerate energy eigenstates the
protection is provided by the system itself. In this case it is actually
possible to measure the Schr\&quot;odinger wave via measurements on a single system.
This fact provides an argument in favor of associating physical reality with a
quantum state of a single system, challenging the usual ensemble
interpretation. We also believe that the complete description of a quantum
system requires a two-state vector formalism involving (in addition to the
usual one)a future quantum state evolving backwards in time. Protective
measurements testing the two-state vector reality are constructed.
</description><date>1994-11-27</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:gr-qc/9411073</identifier></header><metadata><title>Decoherence, Re-coherence, and the Black Hole Information Paradox</title><description>  We analyze a system consisting of an oscillator coupled to a field. With the
field traced out as an environment, the oscillator loses coherence on a very
short {\it decoherence timescale}; but, on a much longer {\it relaxation
timescale}, predictably evolves into a unique, pure (ground) state. This
example of {\it re-coherence} has interesting implications both for the
interpretation of quantum theory and for the loss of information during black
hole evaporation. We examine these implications by investigating the
intermediate and final states of the quantum field, treated as an open system
coupled to an unobserved oscillator.
</description><date>1994-11-29</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:cond-mat/9412005</identifier></header><metadata><title>Dynamics of Quantum Collapse in Energy Measurements</title><description>  The influence of continuous measurements of energy with a finite accuracy is
studied in various quantum systems through a restriction of the Feynman
path-integrals around the measurement result. The method, which is equivalent
to consider an effective Schr\&quot;odinger equation with a non-Hermitian
Hamiltonian, allows one to study the dynamics of the wavefunction collapse. A
numerical algorithm for solving the effective Schr\&quot;odinger equation is
developed and checked in the case of a harmonic oscillator. The situations, of
physical interest, of a two-level system and of a metastable quantum-well are
then discussed. In the first case the Zeno inhibition observed in quantum
optics experiments is recovered and extended to nonresonant transitions, in the
second one we propose to observe inhibition of spontaneous decay in mesoscopic
heterostructures. In all the considered examples the effect of the continuous
measurement of energy is a freezing of the evolution of the system proportional
to the accuracy of the measurement itself.
</description><date>1994-12-01</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:gr-qc/9412005</identifier></header><metadata><title>Is Quantum Mechanics Compatible with a Deterministic Universe? Two
  Interpretations of Quantum Probabilities</title><description>  Two problems will be considered: the question of hidden parameters and the
problem of Kolmogorovity of quantum probabilities. Both of them will be
analyzed from the point of view of two distinct understandings of quantum
mechanical probabilities. Our analysis will be focused, as a particular
example, on the Aspect-type EPR experiment. It will be shown that the quantum
mechanical probabilities appearing in this experiment can be consistently
understood as conditional probabilities without any paradoxical consequences.
Therefore, nothing implies in the Aspect experiment that quantum theory is
incompatible with a deterministic universe.
</description><date>1994-12-01</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:gr-qc/9412006</identifier></header><metadata><title>Gravity and Geometric Phases</title><description>  The behavior of a quantum test particle satisfying the Klein-Gordon equation
in a certain class of 4 dimensional stationary space-times is examined. In a
space-time of a spinning cosmic string, the wave function of a particle in a
box is shown to acquire a geometric phase when the box is transported around a
closed path surrounding the string. When interpreted as an Aharonov-Anandan
geometric phase, the effect is shown to be related to the Aharonov-Bohm effect.
</description><date>1994-12-01</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:gr-qc/9412012</identifier></header><metadata><title>Classical and quantum inertia: A matter of principles</title><description>  A simple, general discussion of the problem of inertia is provided both in
classical physics and in the quantum world. After briefly reviewing the
classical principles of equivalence (weak (WEP), Einstein (EEP), strong (SEP)),
I pass to a presentation of several equivalence statements in nonrelativistic
quantum mechanics and for quantum field vacuum states. It is suggested that a
reasonable type of preferred quantum field vacua may be considered: those
possessing stationary spectra of their vacuum fluctuations with respect to
accelerated classical trajectories
</description><date>1994-12-03</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:hep-th/9412046</identifier></header><metadata><title>Speedup in quantum computation is associated with attenuation of
  processing probability</title><description>  Quantum coherence allows the computation of an arbitrary number of distinct
computational paths in parallel. Based on quantum parallelism it has been
conjectured that exponential or even larger speedups of computations are
possible. Here it is shown that, although in principle correct, any speedup is
accompanied by an associated attenuation of detection rates. Thus, on the
average, no effective speedup is obtained relative to classical
(nondeterministic) devices.
</description><date>1994-12-06</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:hep-th/9412047</identifier></header><metadata><title>Quantum computation and complexity theory</title><description>  The Hilbert space formalism of quantum mechanics is reviewed with emphasis on
applications to quantum computing. Standard interferomeric techniques are used
to construct a physical device capable of universal quantum computation. Some
consequences for recursion theory and complexity theory are discussed.
</description><date>1994-12-06</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:hep-th/9412048</identifier></header><metadata><title>The diagonalization method in quantum recursion theory</title><description>  As quantum parallelism allows the effective co-representation of classical
mutually exclusive states, the diagonalization method of classical recursion
theory has to be modified. Quantum diagonalization involves unitary operators
whose eigenvalues are different from one.
</description><date>1994-12-06</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:hep-th/9412167</identifier></header><metadata><title>Hilbert Space Representation of the Minimal Length Uncertainty Relation</title><description>  The existence of a minimal observable length has long been suggested, in
quantum gravity, as well as in string theory. In this context a generalized
uncertainty relation has been derived which quantum theoretically describes the
minimal length as a minimal uncertainty in position measurements. Here we study
in full detail the quantum mechanical structure which underlies this
uncertainty relation.
</description><date>1994-12-19</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:quant-ph/9412001</identifier></header><metadata><title>Photon Statistics of a Two-Mode Squeezed Vacuum</title><description>  We investigate the general case of the photon distribution of a two-mode
squeezed vacuum and show that the distribution of photons among the two modes
depends on four parameters: two squeezing parameters, the relative phase
between the two oscillators and their spatial orientation. The distribution of
the total number of photons depends only on the two squeezing parameters. We
derive analytical expressions and present pictures for both distributions.
</description><date>1994-12-21</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:gr-qc/9412067</identifier></header><metadata><title>On the Consistent Histories Approach to Quantum Mechanics</title><description>  We review the consistent histories formulations of quantum mechanics
developed by Griffiths, Omn\`es and Gell-Mann and Hartle, and describe the
classification of consistent sets. We illustrate some general features of
consistent sets by a few simple lemmas and examples. We consider various
interpretations of the formalism, and examine the new problems which arise in
reconstructing the past and predicting the future. It is shown that Omn\`es'
characterisation of true statements --- statements which can be deduced
unconditionally in his interpretation --- is incorrect. We examine critically
Gell-Mann and Hartle's interpretation of the formalism, and in particular their
discussions of communication, prediction and retrodiction, and conclude that
their explanation of the apparent persistence of quasiclassicality relies on
assumptions about an as yet unknown theory of experience. Our overall
conclusion is that the consistent histories approach illustrates the need to
supplement quantum mechanics by some selection principle in order to produce a
fundamental theory capable of unconditional predictions.
</description><date>1994-12-22</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:quant-ph/9412002</identifier></header><metadata><title>The Emergence of Classicality via Decoherence: Beyond the
  Caldeira-Legget Environment</title><description>  Maximally predictive states, as defined in recent work by Zurek, Habib and
Paz, are studied for more elaborate environment models than a linear coupling.
An environment model which includes spatial correlations in the noise is
considered in the non-dissipative regime. The Caldeira-Leggett model is also
reconsidered in the context of an averaging procedure which produces a
completely positive form for the quantum master equation. In both cases, the
maximally predictive states for the harmonic oscillator are the coherent
states, which is the same result found by Zurek,Habib and Paz for the
Caldeira-Legget environment.
</description><date>1994-12-22</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:quant-ph/9412003</identifier></header><metadata><title>String Theory, Black Holes and Klein's Lemma</title><description>  This is a writeup of a talk given at the Oskar Klein Centenery Symposium,
Stockholm, September 19-21, 1994. It is an essay on the black hole information
paradox and its connection with thermodynamics and the foundations of quantum
mechanics.
</description><date>1994-12-23</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:quant-ph/9412004</identifier></header><metadata><title>Strong Determinism vs. Computability</title><description>  Are minds subject to laws of physics? Are the laws of physics computable? Are
conscious thought processes computable? Currently there is little agreement as
to what are the right answers to these questions. Penrose goes one step further
and asserts that: {\it a radical new theory is indeed needed, and I am
suggesting, moreover, that this theory, when it is found, will be of an
essentially non-computational character.} The aim of this paper is three fold:
1) to examine the incompatibility between the hypothesis of strong determinism
and computability, 2) to give new examples of uncomputable physical laws, and
3) to discuss the relevance of G\&quot;odel's Incompleteness Theorem in refuting the
claim that an algorithmic theory---like strong AI---can provide an adequate
theory of mind. Finally, we question the adequacy of the theory of computation
to discuss physical laws and thought processes.
</description><date>1994-12-23</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:quant-ph/9412005</identifier></header><metadata><title>On the Stronger Statement of Levinson's Theorem for the Dirac Equation</title><description>  Recently a stronger statement of Levinson's theorem for the Dirac equation
was presented, where the limits of the phase shifts at $E=\pm M$ are related to
the numbers of nodes of radial functions at the same energies, respectively.
However, in this letter we show that this statement has to be modified because
the limits of the phase shifts may be negative for the Dirac equation.
</description><date>1994-12-26</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:quant-ph/9412006</identifier></header><metadata><title>Kochen-Specker theorem for 8-dimensional space</title><description>  A Kochen-Specker contradiction is produced with 36 vectors in a real
8-dimensional Hilbert space. These vectors can be combined into 30 distinct
projection operators (14 of rank 2, and 16 of rank 1). A state-specific variant
of this contradiction requires only 13 vectors, a remarkably low number for 8
dimensions.
</description><date>1994-12-26</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:quant-ph/9412007</identifier></header><metadata><title>Infinite matrices may violate the associative law</title><description>  The momentum operator for a particle in a box is represented by an infinite
order Hermitian matrix $P$. Its square $P^2$ is well defined (and diagonal),
but its cube $P^3$ is ill defined, because $P P^2\neq P^2 P$. Truncating these
matrices to a finite order restores the associative law, but leads to other
curious results.
</description><date>1994-12-26</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:quant-ph/9412008</identifier></header><metadata><title>A general formulation of discrete-time quantum mechanics, restrictions
  on the action and the relation of unitarity to the existence theorem for
  initial-value problems</title><description>  A general formlulation for discrete-time quantum mechanics, based on
Feynman's method in ordinary quantum mechanics, is presented. It is shown that
the ambiguities present in ordinary quantum mechanics (due to noncommutativity
of the operators), are no longer present here. Then the criteria for the
unitarity of the evolution operator is examined. It is shown that the unitarity
of the evolution operator puts restrictions on the form of the action, and also
implies the existence of a solution for the classical initial-value problem.
</description><date>1994-12-28</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:quant-ph/9412009</identifier></header><metadata><title>Superconvergent Perturbation Method in Quantum Mechanics</title><description>  An analogue of Kolmogorov's superconvergent perturbation theory in classical
mechanics is constructed for self adjoint operators. It is different from the
usual Rayleigh--Schr\&quot;odinger perturbation theory and yields expansions for
eigenvalues and eigenvectors in terms of functions of the perturbation
parameter.
</description><date>1994-12-30</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:quant-ph/9412010</identifier></header><metadata><title>Quantum Averaging I: Poincar\'e--von Zeipel is Rayleigh--Schr\&quot;odinger</title><description>  An exact analogue of the method of averaging in classical mechanics is
constructed for self--adjoint operators. It is shown to be completely
equivalent to the usual Rayleigh--Schr\&quot;odinger perturbation theory but gives
the sums over intermediate states in closed form expressions. The anharmonic
oscillator and the Henon--Heiles system are treated as examples to illustrate
the quantum averaging method.
</description><date>1994-12-30</date></metadata></record><record><header><identifier>oai:arXiv.org:quant-ph/9412011</identifier></header><metadata><title>Two Mode Quantum Systems: Invariant Classification of Squeezing
  Transformations and Squeezed States</title><description>  A general analysis of squeezing transformations for two mode systems is given
based on the four dimensional real symplectic group $Sp(4,\Re)\/$. Within the
framework of the unitary metaplectic representation of this group, a
distinction between compact photon number conserving and noncompact photon
number nonconserving squeezing transformations is made. We exploit the
$Sp(4,\Re)-SO(3,2)\/$ local isomorphism and the $U(2)\/$ invariant squeezing
criterion to divide the set of all squeezing transformations into a two
parameter family of distinct equivalence classes with representative elements
chosen for each class. Familiar two mode squeezing transformations in the
literature are recognized in our framework and seen to form a set of measure
zero. Examples of squeezed coherent and thermal states are worked out. The need
to extend the heterodyne detection scheme to encompass all of $U(2)\/$ is
emphasized, and known experimental situations where all $U(2)\/$ elements can
be reproduced are briefly described.
</description><date>1994-12-31</date></metadata></record></ListRecords>